[music]
Do you know
which documents are required for making a health insurance claim
if you must watch the video till the end let's
start
today I will tell you that it is
very important to make an appointment [praise] it is
equally important to make the necessary documents
while doing it it helps in
completing the necessary tasks in a hassle free and peaceful manner
and you will
get quality insurance company and if you are getting
treatment in a hospital then you
must subscribe and with it the required documents select the
option select
mediclaim
policy
policy holder name and with this the
hospital will have to
fill the hospital's ambulance form of the admitting document
and this form will have to be
submitted along with other required documents
secondly
enter the number related to this policy of the company from which you are buying the health insurance policy and you are given the number and for 1 minute you
can check the voter ID card aadhar card passport the doctor has to check the
medical test and there is a
group of subscription that you have linked the necessary benefits to the doctor
whatever expenses have been incurred should be deducted
from the hospital
discharge from the hospital so we can do it this way
Related information is
allegedly
appointed during hospitalization. Please
subscribe
and my voice mail
includes your pen accomplishment. You
need to submit pharmacy verses so that
in case of company
you will need to copy and
do so. If
anyone
needs any information related to this, let's get
started. That's all for today. See you
in the next video. Thank you
[Music]